yammer.com 2012-12-26

# Yammer : Privacy Policy - About Us

Privacy is fundamental to Yammer. Each company or organization on Yammer lives in a separate Network that assures the privacy of its Members and the User Content posted in that Network. Here’s how it works:

Click here to hide details.  
This privacy policy was last modified on February 25, 2011.

Welcome to [www.yammer.com](http://www.yammer.com/) (“Website”). We are happy that you have chosen to visit our Website and learn more about our company. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Website. We will not use or share your Personal Information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

In this Privacy Policy the term “[www.yammer.com](http://www.yammer.com/)” refers to our Website, the homepage of which is located at [www.yammer.com](http://www.yammer.com/); the terms “us” or “we” or “our” refers to Yammer, Inc. (“Yammer”), the owner of [www.yammer.com](http://www.yammer.com/), and the terms “you” or “user” refer to the user or viewer of[ www.yammer.com](http://www.yammer.com/). Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Use.

When using Yammer, there are general elements of our service that you should know. First, your network of contacts is defined by your company or organization’s email domain. To join a network, you must confirm your email address and it must match the email domain of your company. Additionally, only people in your network can view other member profiles and feeds. Companies that “claim” their network can impose additional security requirements beyond those described in this Privacy Policy. Examples of such restrictions include secure sessions, password policies and restricting access to the internal protocol range of their virtual private network. Additionally, companies that claim their network own the user generated content of their employees. Yammer does not own such user generated content and network administrators can request that user generated content posted to their network be securely exported to a company designated destination for archival and backup purposes. Yammer’s administrative tools do not allow our employees to view messages in a network. Access to our database is granted only to our technicians on a case-by-case basis to troubleshoot specific technical issues, or as may be required by law. For further details on using Yammer, please refer to our Terms of Use Agreement, located here.

Yammer is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy policy covers the Website [www.yammer.com](http://www.yammer.com/ "Yammer.com"). Because this Website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact [privacy@yammer.com](mailto:privacy@yammer.com) or send mail to Privacy, Yammer Inc. 410 Townsend Street Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94107. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url "truste watchdog"). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with Yammer to resolve your concerns.

Yammer complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Yammer has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view the company’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

As we update and expand our Website, this Privacy Policy may change, so please check this web page for updates to our Privacy Policy.

### Collection of Information

When you visit our Website we may collect information regarding your visit from your computer. Such information helps us to determine information about how you found our Website, the date that you visited our Website and search engines that may have led you to our Website. We collect this information in order to continually improve and enhance the functionality of [www.yammer.com](https://www.yammer.com/ "Yammer")

Generally, you may provide us with two types of information, User Content, which may include Personal Information, and Website Usage Information, both of which are discussed in greater detail below.

### Personal Information You Choose to Provide

In order to make your visits to our Website as enjoyable as possible, we may ask you for Personal Information. Personal Information includes, for example, your name and email address, both of which you are asked to provide when registering with Yammer. Below is a description of some of the ways that you may provide Personal Information to us, as well as further details on how we may use such Personal Information.

  1. ###### Sign-Up Information and Profile

You provide us with Personal Information, such as your name and email address, when you register a Member account with the Website. You may also choose to add information, such as a photo, to your profile.

  2. ###### Contact Us/Feedback

If you email us through the [www.yammer.com](https://www.yammer.com/) contact us link on our Website, we may ask you for information such as your name and email address so we can respond to your questions and comments. If you choose to correspond with us via email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our response to you. In certain cases, and with your permission, we may post content from your emails to us on the Yammer Website.

  3. ###### Questionnaires and Surveys

We may occasionally ask users of our Website to complete online surveys and opinion polls about their activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us better serve you and improve the usefulness of Yammer. In requesting your participation in these surveys we may ask you to provide you name and email address to us.

  4. ###### User Content

Our Website offers its users the opportunity to share User Content – for instance, on bulletin boards and blogs and in chat rooms. If you choose to use these features, you should be aware that any Personal Information you submit through these features can be read, collected, or used by other viewers of these forums and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums.

  5. ###### Import Contacts

We utilize an import contacts feature to help you keep in touch with your contacts and other members. We make it easy for you to invite people from your email address book to join you on our Website. You can manually import a file from your email program or you can provide us with your email user name and password and the Yammer program will import your email contacts for you. When you import your contacts, we will ask you if you wish to invite or follow your colleagues from your same domain. If you indicate that you would like to follow them, we will send them an invitation from you (with a return address of [noreply@yammer.com](mailto:noreply@yammer.com)) to activate a Yammer account and join the same domain network as you. We may also send one reminder message after the original invitation if we do not hear back from them. People you invite to join the Website may opt out of receiving further emails from Yammer as described in the Rights to Opt In/Opt Out section below.

### Website Usage Information

  1. ###### Cookies

We may use “cookies” on or in connection with our Website to maintain information about you. A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. Yammer employs the use of both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser.

When you visit our Website, our computer may ask your computer for permission to employ the use of a session or persistent cookie. Our Website will then send a cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits our Website to access the cookies it has already sent to you and not the cookies sent to you by other websites.

Most web browsers can be adjusted to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, our Website or certain areas or features of our Website.

  2. ###### Clear GIFs

We may also use “Clear GIFs” (aka “web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies in our Website and/or in our communications with you. A Clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which helps us to verify an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. Clear GIFs allow us to know whether you have viewed a web page prior to visiting our Website and may enable us to relate such information to other information, including your Personal Information. We use information provided from Clear GIFs to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make Yammer better for our users.

  3. ###### IP Address and Clickstream Data

Our servers automatically collect data about your Internet Protocol address when you visit us. When you request pages from our Website, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another website or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Website; the website you visit after this Website; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Website or a referral website; and other web usage activity and data logged by our web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with Personal Information.

Any or all of these activities with regard to the above-described Website Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our third-party service providers. (See third-parties Sharing Information with Third Parties section below).

### Rights to Opt In/Opt Out

You have the right to “opt in” and/or “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, if you are prompted to provide Personal Information on this Website or in connection with our communications to you, you may have the opportunity to elect whether you would like to receive such correspondence from us. You may opt out of Yammer’s promotional e-mails by clicking on the opt-out or “unsubscribe” link within the email you receive. You can also make this request by sending an email to [help@yammer.com](mailto:help@yammer.com), specifying whether: (i) you would like to opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from Yammer in general, or just via e-mail, postal mail and/or by phone, and/or whether (ii) you would only like to opt out of certain of Yammer’s e-newsletters or correspondence.

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We will use your Personal Information to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Website Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including (without limitation) any of our other websites and third parties. If you choose to import your address book contacts as part of Yammer’s invitation process, we may store those names and emails and display them to other Network members on the Website in order to customize the Service for you and to enable you and coworkers in your Network to generate subsequent invitations. We may send you notices (for example, in the form of emails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies, events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Rights to Opt In/Opt Out section above.

In addition, we may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and emails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. Yammer will not share, rent or sell your Personal Information to other parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

  1. ###### Service Providers

We may use third-party partners to help us operate and maintain our Website and deliver our products and services. We may also share your Personal Information and Website Usage Information with our service providers and other third parties (“Affiliated Parties”) that provide products or services for or through this Website or for our business (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, communications providers, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, credit card processing companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

Third-party service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the Personal Information and Website Usage Information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements, or otherwise subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

  2. ###### Aggregate Statistics

We may disclose non-personally identifiable aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and emails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports, which do not describe or identify any individual user. Information relating to aggregate statistics may be collected through the use of third-party cookies and other third party tracking devices.

  3. ###### Legally Compelled Disclosures

We may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with a judicial or court order or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Website, the users of the Website, and/or our Affiliated Parties; or (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our Website, us, or third parties.

  4. ###### Business Transfer

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through this Website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If this occurs, we will notify you as described in “Updates to our Privacy Policy”

### Consent to Worldwide Transfer and Processing of Personal Data

By providing Personal Information to us through this Website, you agree that it may be used by us and our Affiliated Parties for the purposes described herein and you further understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, which may have different privacy laws from your country of residence and which may afford varying levels of protection for your Personal Information. Regardless of the laws in place in these countries, we will treat the privacy of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By providing your Personal Information to this Website, you consent to our transmission to, and processing of your information in, any jurisdiction, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Your Access and Correction Rights

You retain the right to decline to submit Personal Information through Yammer, in which case Yammer may not be able to provide certain services to you. However, if you choose to provide Personal Information to Yammer, we will provide you with the ability to access, correct, update or delete the Personal Information you have provided to this Website by emailing  [help@yammer.com](mailto:help@yammer.com). We will respond to your request within 30 days. However, before we are able to provide you with any information or correct any inaccuracies, we may ask you to verify your identity and provide other details to help us to respond to your request.

### Third-Party Websites

When you are on this Website you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other websites, including other websites operated by Yammer or by unaffiliated third parties. These websites may collect Personal Information about you, and because this Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites, you should review the privacy policies of such other websites to see how they treat your Personal Information.

### Privacy of Minors

This Website is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen on our Website. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen on our Website, we will delete the information from our records.

### Security

Yammer uses commercially reasonable and industry standard physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We also use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to transmit sensitive information. While Yammer endeavors to protect the security and integrity of sensitive Personal Information provided to this Website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

If you contact us by email or a “contact us” or similar feature on the Website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. An unaffiliated third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email. You consent to our use of email as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please email us at [help@yammer.com](mailto:help@yammer.com) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.

### Updates to Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online information practices. We will post a prominent notice on this Website to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Policy and indicate at the top of the statement when it was most recently updated. To see the most recent changes, made February 25, 2011, please click [here](https://www.yammer.com/about/privacy#privacy-policy-lightbox "Privacy Policy Updates")

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review, delete or update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us at the following address:

Name: Attn: Yammer Privacy  
Address: 410 Townsend St. Suite 300, San Francisco CA 94109  
Telephone: (415) 968-5851  
Fax: (415) 777-5977  
Email: [help@yammer.com](mailto:help@yammer.com)

* * *
